Evi Nur Annisa

Jl Mrisi, Gn. Cilik, Tirnonirmolo, Yogyakarta 55184 082138854442

evinurannisa00@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/evinannisa/ https://github.com/eviannisaa

Summary

Hello, my name is Evi Nur Annisa. I'm Frontend Developer based in Yogyakarta with 2 years of experience. Currently, I'm focused on developing my portfolio as Frontend Developer and enhance my skills as a UI/UX Designer. Also, I am still and counting to make a new journey and to be a better Evi each day. Take your time, check my resume and see my skills. Thank you..

Education

AMIKOM YOGYAKARTA UNIVERSITY

Yogyakarta, Indonesia

2019 - 2022

- Diploma, Informatics Engineering. GPA 3.82Teaching/Practicum Assistant
 - Introduction to Computer division of Mobile Development
 - Awarding Amikom Computer Club
 - Committee of Penggalian Potensi Mahasiswa
 - 3rd place Design UI/UX at "Gelar Karya Mahasiswa D3 Fakultas Ilmu Komputer Universitas Amikom Yogyakarta"

Work Experience

PT. Infosys Solusi Terpadu (IST) Frontend Developer

Yogyakarta, Indonesia Feb 2023 – Present

- Build banking web application, create a stable and consistent website according to the design, integrate with APIs, fixing issue, etc
- Able to build web-based applications with react typescript, style components and tailwind css
- Creating webpage layouts, code writing, and making adjustments based on client feedback
- Implemented UI and UX designs to web
- Collaborated with product team members to implement new feature developments

PT. Media Kreasi Abadi (MKA) Internship (MBKM) Frontend Developer

Balikpapan, Indonesia

Feb 2022 – Jul 2022

- Learn frontend basics developers such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Using Version Control (git), Build Tools, Layouting and more
- Able to build web-based applications with react typescript and about basic javascript, basic react and also basic typescript
- Slicing UI/UX designs to HTML, CSS

GCM FOUNDATION (Geschool)

Internship Frontend Developer

Yogyakarta, Indonesia Sept 2021 – Jan 2022

- Implemented websites and landing pages from concept through deployment
- Assessed UX and UI designs for technical feasibility
- Collaborated with product team members to implement new feature developments

AMIKOM YOGYAKARTA UNIVERSITY

Practicum Assistant of Web Design 1

Yogyakarta, Indonesia Feb 2021 – Aug 2021

- Practice and explain HTML, CSS and JavaScript modules to students
- Reviewing lessons or lectures with students on a one-on-one basis or in small groups
- Supervising students in class and tracking attendance, grading assignments and calculating activity score

Leadership & Activities

BEM KM AMIKOM YOGYAKARTA UNIVERSITY Ministry of Advocacy

Yogyakarta, Indonesia Feb 2021 – Feb 2022

- Capture the aspirations of all amikom students
- Oversee internal and external issues on campus
- Establish communication with the Chancellor regarding student welfare needs
- Pioneer of the vaccination program, scholarship and all aspirations for Amikom students

Himpunan Mahasiswa Diploma Teknik Informatika Treasurer

Yogyakarta, Indonesia Sep 2020 – Dec 2021

- Oversee the general financial management of an organizing committee
- Plan and keep track of budgets within the organization, collect, deposit and keep track of funds write cheques and provide financial reports regularly

Portfolio

• Portfolio resmi saya:

https://evinannisa.github.io/eviannisa/

• Repository "buildwithangga" Slicing to HTML, CSS with Bootstrap:

https://github.com/eviannisaa/joinbwa

• Platform Education Parenting:

https://github.com/Media-Kreasi-Abadi/frontend-tim-j-batch-2

• Login page geschool:

https://madrasahdiy.net/ . http://gunungkidul.geschool.net/ . http://div.geschool.net/

• Assesment Kompetensi Minimum:

https://github.com/AKM-geschool

• Skordigital Pencak Silat:

https://github.com/New-Skordigital

• Dribble (Design UI/UX):

https://dribbble.com/Evi annisa

Skills and Interests

Skills: HTML CSS, React Js, UI/UX Design (Figma)

Language: Indonesian **Tools:** VsCode and Figma

Interests: Drawing, Music, Gaming, Design UI/UX